const monthLengths = [
    {
        question: 'January',
        answers: ['31'],
    },
    {
        question: 'February',
        answers: ['28', '29'],
    },
    {
        question: 'March',
        answers: ['31'],
    },
    {
        question: 'April',
        answers: ['30'],
    },
    {
        question: 'May',
        answers: ['31'],
    },
    {
        question: 'June',
        answers: ['30'],
    },
    {
        question: 'July',
        answers: ['31'],
    },
    {
        question: 'August',
        answers: ['31'],
    },
    {
        question: 'September',
        answers: ['30'],
    },
    {
        question: 'October',
        answers: ['31'],
    },
    {
        question: 'November',
        answers: ['30'],
    },
    {
        question: 'December',
        answers: ['31'],
    },
];

export default monthLengths;
